We're crabs in the
right now Yeah okay
I think it's just
like a waste of
energy to spend too
time on that And
I'm about the viewing
of the compass of
balance right So number
one is that I
think that there is
a degree of understanding
that's required for journalists
to be able to
complete the balance of
what is a transaction
in that piece or
any kind of topic
that they're There are
a of folks who
opining on like market
norms for DPI They're
opining on say LP
dollars on it They're
on how LPs want
or what VC should
do and da da
da But there's like
so like maybe they
would understand 20 of
actually the dynamics and
what are in the
larger limited partner agreement
clauses and some of
those things And the
thing is I'm not
saying that to kind
of fault anyone I'm
saying that even within
us as VCs like
when we started raising
our funds we didn't
even know what were
the market terms with
our LPs Then we
ask our and the
whether they knew it
or they didn't know
it they have to
act like they know
it Do know I
mean And so everyone
was like trying to
like shape what the
norms is as they
went You're setting it
as you go Yeah
okay So nobody knows
right Nobody knows what
the are And then
we talk about this
isn't the norm They
analyze it No that's
the norm Everyone's got
their own norm right
And then we blast
around this market Oh
you're off market That's
such an off market
term right